Finding Aid for the Horace Tapscott Papers PASC-M.0237
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound Recordings, Series 1.
  - Assorted Identified Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Sunday Concert in Black Music at Foshay Series 4, The Quintet, Side 1, 1970 March 8; pasc-m_0237_037_006a; Horace Tapscott Quintet; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:30:50) (Box 37, Case 6)
      Content Note: Personnel- Horace Tapscott, Arthur Blythe, David Bryant, Walter Savage, Everette Brown. Compositions- The Grip, Effie, Cliff MacLane Speaks out, The grip. Transcribed from container: #8370 YOU
    - Sunday Concert in Black Music at Foshay Series 4, The Quintet, Side 2, 1970 March 8; pasc-m_0237_037_006b; Horace Tapscott Quintet; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:54) (Box 37, Case 6)
    - Sunday Concert in Black Music at Foshay Series 4, Carter-Bradford Quartet, Side 1, 1970 March 8; pasc-m_0237_037_007a; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:11) (Box 37, Case 7)
      Content Note: Personnel-John Carter, Bobby Bradford, Tommy Williamson- bass, Bruz Freeman- percussion. Compositions- Sticks and Stones, Seeking, Call to the Festival. Trancribed from container: #8370 YOU Transcribed from insert: Note! CK! Other Side of tape!
    - Sunday Concert in Black Music at Foshay Series 4, Carter-Bradford Quartet, Side 2, 1970 March 8; pasc-m_0237_037_007b; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:15:36) (Box 37, Case 7)
    - Foshay Jr. H.S. Concert, April 5, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 18)
      Guido Sinclair Sextet
      Personnel: Guido, alto sax; Herbie Baker, piano; Willie Samprite, trumpet; Robert Miranda, bass; Steve Solder, drums; Ernest S, flute; Ray S, tenor sax
      Compositions: E.P. -- All About You -- Black, Brown and Yellow -- Semaj -- E.P.
    - Year of UGMAA, April 7, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 19)
      Personnel: Herbie Baker, piano; Robert Miranda, bass; Steve Solder, drums.
      Compositions: J.O.B. -- O'Grande Amour -- Flight 17 -- Saint Michael.
    - S.F.U.S.C. (room 119), April 28, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 20)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest Staughter, flute and baritone sax; Edwin Pleasant, flute; Black Arthur, alto sax; Will Connell, alto sax; Cerion Middleton III, tenor sax; Ray Straughter, tenor sax; Robert S., trombone; Butch Morris, cornet; Ike W, trumpet; David B; Walter S; Everett; Aminifu (Amina), rhythm; Ester, rhythm; Porter and Wilbur, rhythm; Linda and Tamu, rhythm.
      Compositions: Cathedral -- Carnival -- Vision -- Coronation -- Funeral -- Carnival -- Freedom.
    - The ARK and CBQ at Foshay, May 31, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 23)
      Compositions: Carnival -- Funeral Theme -- LeRoy -- Eye of the Storm.
      Tape 1 of 3.
    - The ARK and CBQ at Foshay, May 31, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 24)
      Compositions: Carnival -- The Funeral -- LeRoy -- In Eye of Storm.
      Tape 2 of 3.
    - KPFK, May 31, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 25)
      Personnel: Tom; Fred Wilson; Fredrick Barter; Larry Smith; Clayton Tucker; James E. Williams; Willy Aoffer; Ted Jones; Ted Watkin; Dennis Matthews; Rudy Jackson; Ted Jones; Leon Thomas; Ed Hamilton; Bernard Sonner.
    - Commentary, June 9, 1970; 1/4" open reel audio tape (Box 73, Folder 2)
      Ric Castberg speaks of the generation gap.
      KPFK 90.7 FM.
    - Jordan High School Black Music Workshop, June 14, 1970; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 73, Folder 3)
      Compositions include: 16 Bar Blues -- Soul Waltz -- Cousin Mary -- Comin' Home Baby -- Sonny's Dream -- Banana -- 16 Bar Blues.
      Tape 1 of 4.
    - Jordan High School Black Music Workshop, June 14, 1970; 1/4" open reel audio tape (Box 73, Folder 4)
      Compositions: Forest Flower -- Emancipation Blues -- Viva Tirada -- Emerge! -- Why Don't You Listen -- Effie.
      Tape 2 of 4.
    - Jordan High School Black Music Workshop, June 14, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      Compositions include: Freedom, Lonesome Lover, Why Don't You Listen (incomplete).
      Tape 3 of 4.
    - Jordan High School Black Music Workshop, June 14, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Why Don't You Listen (end).
      Tape 4 of 4.
    - The Rhetoric of Black Power, March 19, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      Dr Karlyn Campbell, Assistant Professor of Speech - Cal State Los Angeles.
    - UGMAA Show for Omatie, December 7, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Linda Hill, vocal
      Compositions: The Funeral (Warriors All), The Dark Tree, Soft & Furry (Fine Young Thing by Linda Hill), Freedom's Sweet, South Street Exit (Dolphy), Epistrophy, What Love Is (Dolphy), In a Sentimental Mood (Black Quarter), Lover Man
    - UGMAA Show for Omatie, December 7,1970; 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Concert in Black Music Series #2, 1970 February 8; pasc-m_0237_007_010a; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:30:13) (Box 7, Case 10)
      Transcribed from container: Year of UGMAA. 1. Woman- Bobby Bradford, 2. Sticks and Stoned- John Carter
    - Lock High School:year of UGMAA, March 19, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Personnel: Barbara Sherriel, Tapscott Quintet and Lock Jazz Chorus
    - Foshay Jr.H.S.Concert, April 5, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Personnel: Guido, as; Herbie Baker, p; Willie Samprite, tp; Robert Miranda, b; Steve Solder,d; Ernest S, fl; Ray S, ts.
      Compositions: E.P.; All About You, Black, Brown and Yellow, Semaj, E.P.
    - Concert in Bla'mus (Black Music) at Foshay, with the Carter - Bradford Quartet, Azar Lawrence Quartet, and Band from UGMAA, 1970 April 28; pasc-m_0237_073_001a; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; Azar Lawrence Quartet; UGMAA; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:35:02) (Box 73, Case 1)
      Content Note: see accompanying documentation for composition and personnel details
    - Concert in Bla'mus (Black Music) at Foshay, with the Carter - Bradford Quartet, Azar Lawrence Quartet, and Band from UGMAA 1970, 1970 April 19-28; pasc-m_0237_073_001b; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; Azar Lawrence Quartet; UGMAA; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:34:52) (Box 73, Case 1)
    - Christophe, May 3, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 21)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, flute; Edwin P, flute; Chico R, flute; Black Arthur, alto sax; Will C, alto sax; Cerion, tenor sax; Ray S, tenor sax; Robert S, trombone; David B; Walter S; Brother Eddie, conga; Jimmie Hoskins, drums; Butch Morris, cornet; Marcus Hill, pot; vocals: Cynthia, Glenda, Oscar, Charles, Linda Hill. Compositions: Carnival -- Waltz Time -- Funeral -- Coronation -- Cathedral -- Vision.
    - Malcom X, May 19, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 22)
      Story Teller, KPKK
      Personnel: Edwin Teddy Jones, Bob H. DeCoy
    - Foshay Jr. H. S. Arkestra and Chorus, May 31, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Personnel: Carter - Bradford Quartet Compositions: drum solo (Everett),World Peace, the Funeral,Black
      Personnel: drum duet- Everett and Bruz
      Compositions: Eye of the Storm
      Personnel: Community Cultural Orchestra and the Voice
      Composition: The meeting (Elaine Brown)
      Personnel:The Poets of UGMA
      Pieces: Fatifia - black Woman; Sabu- Making War; Kufahamu- " Spiritual"
      Compositions: the Dream (HT), Freedom ( Chico Roberson)
    - Concert in "Black Music" Series at the Malcolm X Center, July 5, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      Compositions include: The Call -- In a Sentimental Mood -- The Grip -- Little A's Chant -- Oleo.
      The Community Cultural Orchestra Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott; Ernest Straughter, flute; Butch Morris, cornet; Jerome, trumpet; Will Connell, Arthur Blythe, alto sax; Ray Straughter, tenor sax; Bert, Guido Sinclair, baritone sax; Lester Robertson; Robert, baritone; David Bryant, Walter S, bass; Everett Brown, Jr.; poets: Wanda C and Caroline; tape techinicians: Linda and Prentice.
    - Jordan High School, June 7, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Compositions: Passion Dance -- Watermelon Man.
    - Memorial Concert for Herbert Keith Baker at the Malcom X Center, 1970 June 21; pasc-m_0237_073_007a; UGMAA; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:24) (Box 73, Case 7)
      Content Note: Compositions- C.C.O., Little A's Chant, Prance Dance, Last Time I Saw Herbie (poem Cheryl Solder), Elophius, Footprints, (no name). Personnel- Horace Tapscott, Lester Robertson, Nate Morgan, Michael Stanton-piano, Azar Lawrence, Ernest Straughter-flute; Black Arthur-alto sax, Will Connell-alto sax, Cerion Middleton III, Ray Straughter-tenor sax, Bert Simon-baritone, Robert Sims-clarinet, Doug Morris-cornet, David Bryant, Everett Brown, Jr.
    - Memorial Concert for Herbert Keith Baker at the Malcom X Center, 1970 June 21; pasc-m_0237_073_007b; UGMAA; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:35) (Box 73, Case 7)
    - Concert in Black Music at Widney High School, Carter-Bradford Quartet plus One Selections, 1971 July 11; pasc-m_0237_022_006a; Horace Tapscott Quintet; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:28:20) (Box 22, Case 6)
      Transcribed from container: #71171 YOUS. Content Note: Personnel- Bobby; John; Tom W; Bruz F; Nate Morgan, piano. The Arkestra. Personnel: Nate Morgan, piano; Ernest Straughter, flute; Robert Roy, flute and piccolo; Cerion; Ray S; Black Arthur; Will C; Jimmy, baritone sax; Al Hall, trombone; butch; Walter S, trumpet; Everett Brown, Jr.; Cojoe; David Bryant; vocals: Aminifu, Chanima, Isis, Charles, Linda Hill, Kito.
    - Concert in Black Music Widney High School, The Arkestra-Ho-Ta, 1971 July 11; pasc-m_0237_022_006b; Horace Tapscott Quintet; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:15:10) (Box 22, Case 6)
    - Malcolm X Center concert, July 12, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 27)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, flute; Arthur, alto sax; Will C, alto sax; Cerion M; Bert, baritone; Lester R; Robert, trombone; Butch M; Jerome, trumpet; David B; Walter S; Everett; Greg T, drums
      Compositions: Freedom -- Future Sally's Time.
    - Quartet at Widney High School, July 19,1970 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Black Arthur; David B; Everett
      Compositions: Dark Tree, Drunken Mary
      Personnel: Ernest Staughter, piano; Ray Staughter, tenor sax; Roberto Miranda, bass; John Blue, drums
      Compositions: St. Michael, Ballad for Samuel, Masters at Work
    - Concert at Bing Theatre, LACMA, July 20, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 76, Folder 28)
      Quintet and Voice
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Edwin Jones, flute; Arthur, alto sax; David B; Walter S; Everett; Lemahi, vocal. Compositions: Introduction to a Dream -- Freedom / Chico Roberson -- Pearl / Horace Tapscott -- Lonesome Lover / Max Roach and Abbey Lincoln -- The Funeral, Warriors All / Tapscott and Linda Hill -- Effie / Stanley Cowell.
    - Concert at Bing Theatre, LACMA, July 20, 1970; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 29)
      The Horace Tapscott Community Orchestra. Compositions: The Funeral, The Dark Tree -- The Grip -- The Giant -- Effie.
      Tape 2 of 2.
    - History of My People - University Community Center, 36th st., USC, August 20, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Linda Hill, vocal
      Compositions: Freedom, Dem Folks, The Funeral (Warrior's All), Chants (A Bo' Bo', L'Lemah's, De Light, Praise HIm, Mee; Illehwaae), Imani, Imani (sings), Ghetto (sings), South Wind, South Wind (speaks), The Growth of a People, The Rape/The Theft, East Wind (speaks), The Time, Betta Tighten Up, Imani the JOker, Imani the Giant
    - Greg's Refresher Course - KUSC radio show, Live Concert from USC's Hancock Hall, 1970 August 23; pasc-m_0237_076_031; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:40:35) (Box 76, Case 31)
      Tape 1 of 3. Transcribed from container: Rehearsal Pre-Show. Content note: Personnel- Horace Tapscott-piano, Ernest Cojoe-congas, Linda Hill-vocal. Compositions-bFreedom's Sweet, Abobo/David's Chant (Linda's word/song), Cojoe's Solo, L'Lemahi's Light, Effie, Sticks and Stones, Abstractions for Three Lovers, Eye of the Storm (Bobby B), Greg and Ted Jones talk
    - Greg's Refresher Course - KUSC radio show, Live Concert from USC's Hancock Hall, 1970 August 23; pasc-m_0237_076_032; John Carter & Bobby Bradford Quartet; Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:41:05) (Box 76, Case 32)
      Tape 2 of 3. Content note: Personnel- Horace Tapscott-piano, Ernest Cojoe-congas, Linda Hill-vocal. Compositions-bFreedom's Sweet, Abobo/David's Chant (Linda's word/song), Cojoe's Solo, L'Lemahi's Light, Effie, Sticks and Stones, Abstractions for Three Lovers, Eye of the Storm (Bobby B), Greg and Ted Jones talk
    - Greg's Refresher Course - KUSC radio show, Live Concert from USC's Hancock Hall, Reel 3 of 3, 1970 August 23; pasc-m_0237_076_033; Tapscott, Horace; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:11:05) (Box 76, Case 33)
      Tape 3 of 3. Transcribed from container: #82370 YOU; Flute. Content note: Personnel- Horace Tapscott-piano, Ernest Cojoe-congas, Linda Hill-vocal. Compositions-bFreedom's Sweet, Abobo/David's Chant (Linda's word/song), Cojoe's Solo, L'Lemahi's Light, Effie, Sticks and Stones, Abstractions for Three Lovers, Eye of the Storm (Bobby B), Greg and Ted Jones talk
    - Troubled Waters at Berkeley, August 25, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Personnel: Max Roach; Abbey Lincoln; Stanley Cowell, piano; Charles Tolliver, trumpet; Gary Barth, alto; Reggie Workman, bass
      Compositions: Troubled Waters
    - Rehearsals at Grant's Music Center & Lino's Pad, August 28, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Malik; Semaj; Willie Samprite, etc.
      Compositions: Fo'Fats, Your Child, World Peace
    - South Park, 1970 August 30; pasc-m_0237_041_003; Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra; UGMAA; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:33) (Box 41, Case 3)
      Transcribed from container: South Park #83070 YOU. Side One- "Little A's Chant". Side 2- "Freedom's Sweet". Ernest Cojoe on congas.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra and the Voice of UGMAA, South Park., September 5, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Compositions: Little A's Chant -- Freedom's Sweet.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Ernest Cojoe, congas.
    - Community Cultural Arkestra, September 10, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Kufahamu, spoken word (read poetry). Compositions: Freedom's Sweet -- Warriors All -- Leroy I & II (for Leroy Brooks) / Linda Hill.
    - Edwin Fletcher Jones Memorial, September 20, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      UGMAA Concert in Black Music
      (also T.J. Memorial at the "Citadel")
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, fL; Ray S, alto sax; Butch Morris, cornet; Chico Robertson,fl; Arthur Blythe, tenor sax; Edwin Pleasant, fl; David B, Greg Tell, drums; Nate, Morgan, piano; Ernest Cojoe, congas; Will Connell, as; Lester R, Pobert Sims, tuba; Cerion M, as Tom Williamson, b, Cojoe, congas; Linda Hill, vocal.
      Compositions, part I: E.P.; Little A's Chant, The Funeral, Freedom Suite, Effi, Poets ( maybe including William Marshall)
      Compositions, part II: Little A's Chant, Funeral, the Dream, Freedom
      part III: poetry - Cheryl Solder, Cliff Shaw
    - Edwin Fletcher Jones Memorial, September 20, 1970; 2 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      UGMAA Concert in Black Music (also T.J. Memorial at "The Citadel")
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, flute; Ray S, alto sax, Butch Morris, cornet; Chico Roberson, flute; Arthur Blythe, tenor sax; Edwin Pleasant, flute; David B; Greg Tell, drums; Nate Morgan, paino; Ernest Cojoe, congas; Will Connell, alto sax; Lester R; Robert Sims, tuba; Cerion M, alto sax; Tom Williamson, bass; Cojoe, congas; Linda Hill, vocal
      Compositions: Little A's Chant, Funeral, The Dream, Freedom
    - Edwin Fletcher Jones Memorial, September 20,1970; 3 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Compositions: poetry- Cheryl Solder, Cliff Shaw
    - KPFK FM Radio UGMAA Show (1 of 2), September 22, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano
      Compositions: Vision Music, Warriors All, For J.O.B., St. Michael, Village Dancers
    - KPFK FM Radio UGMAA Show (2 of 2), September 22, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Live at Grant's Music Center, September 23, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      UGMAA Quartet
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ike Williams, flugelhorn; Tom Williamson, bass; Bruz Freeman, drums
      Compositions: Inspirations of Silence (E. Straughter), Eye of the Storm (Bobby Bradford), Resurrection (Ike Williams)
    - Afternon at Rose Gale's House, September 23, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Inspirations of Silence -- In a Sentimental Mood -- Congeniality / Ornette Coleman.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Black Arthur, alto sax; Larry Gales, cello; David Bryant, bass; Everett Brown, Jr.
    - Luper's Studio (Rudolph's), September 26, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      KPFK FM, the UGMAA Show
      Compositions: In Times Like These (Lester Robertson), Little A's Chant, E.P. (Ray Straughter)
    - Luper's (Rudolph's), September 30, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Community Cultural Arkestra
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, conductor; Nate Morgan, paino; Will C, alto sax; Ernest S, flute; Black Arthur, alto sax; Ray S, tenor sax; Cerion, tenor sax; Butch Morris, cornet; Lester R, trombone; Donny Smith, tuba; David B
      Compositions: Azar (Azar Lawrence), Linda (will Connell), Lush Life
    - Luper's (Rudolph's), October 3, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Ernest S, flute; Will C, alto sax; Black Arthur, alto sax; Cerion M, tenor sax; Ray S, tenor sax; Bert, baritone sax; Butch, cornet; Donny, tuba; Lester, trombone; Robert, baritone sax; Wilber, bass; Tom W, bass; Sherman McKinney, cello; Nate, piano; Marcus Hill, congas; Glenda, soprano vocal; Pat, alto vocal; Linda, alto vocal; Luther, vocal; Cheryl, vocal; Mamie, vocal; Omatie (Leland Hill?), vocal; and the kids: Rashied, Laurence, Niles (vocals?)
      Compositions: Lino's Pad, The Meeting, Linda, Azar, Lush Life
    - Live Broadcast, Hancock Hall, USC - "Greg's Refresher Course," KUSC 91.5 FM, November 8, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      The Community Cultural Arkestra, Locke H.S. Jazz Chorus
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Black Arthur; Ernest Cojoe, congas; Donny, tuba; Ray S, tenor sax; Ernest, flute; Cerion, tenor sax and voice; Linda Hill, vocal; Greg Kufahamu, announcer
      Compositions: Little A's Chant, Bird Song (Linda Hill), The Giant Is Awakened, Warriors All, Why Don't You Listen?
    - Live Broadcast, Hancock Hall, USC - "Greg's Refresher Course," KUSC 91.5 FM, November 8, 1970; 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Compositions: Why Don't You Listen?, Lush Life, The Call, Effi
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Sound Ray's, October 10, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      The Arkestra at Widney H.S.
      Personnel: Ray S, tenor sax; Linda Hill, piano; Sherman McKinney, bass; Greg Tell, drums
      Compositions: Deluge, All Blues, Thoughts of Our Time (Ray S & Sherman McKinney), Into the Next
      Poetry by Lemahi (one of Linda's other names)
    - Malcolm X Center, Concert in Black Music, October 11, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Personnel: Ernest, flute; Chico, flute, Black Arthur; Will C; Cerion; Ray S; Bertm baritone sax; Butch; Jerome, tumpet; Lester; Robert, baritone sax; Donny, tuba; David B; Wilber Morris, bass; Sherman McKinney, cello; Greg Tell, drums; Nate Morgan, piano
      Compositions: E.P. (Ray S), Azar, In Times Like These, Inspirations of Silence (Ernest S)
    - Malcolm X Center, Concert in Black Music, October 11, 1970; 2 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Luper's - Full Moon Concert, October 14, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Ernest, flute; Jerome, flute; Butch; Will C; Black Arthur; Cerion; Ray S; Bert, baritone sax; Lester; Robert, baritone sax; David B; Wilber, bass; Sherman McKinney, bass; Everett; Greg Tell, drums; Linda, vocal
      Compositions: Freedom's Sweet, 400 Years, David's Chant, drum solo, The Dream, Freedum
    - Luper's - Full Moon Concert, October 14, 1970; 2 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - KPFK - The UGMAA Show - For Teddy Jones, October 17, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      Compositions: Leon -- St. Michael -- The Grip -- Effi.
    - The Citadel - Concert in Black Music, October 18,1970; 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Community Cultural Arkestra and the Voice of UGMAA
      Personnel: Ernest; Black Arthur; Cerion; Ray S; Bert; Butch; Jerome; Lester; Robert; Wilber; David B; Greg T; Everett; Horace Tapscott; Patricia; Linda
      Compositions: The Giant (excerpt), E.P., Little A's Chant; Azar; The Call; The Funeral; Nate Morgan Quartet
    - The Citadel - Concert in Black Music, October 18,1970; 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Carmel Crunk, October 25, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Take 1 Carmel Crunk.
    - Carmel Crunk, October 25, 1970; 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Compositions: Freedom's Sweet -- drum solo -- The Dream -- Freedom -- Poets of UGMAA.
      Community Cultural Arkestra.
    - Concert at Foshay, October 25, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Personnel: Ernest, flute; Butch, trumpet; Troy, trumpet; Jerome, trumpet; Black, alto; Will, alto; Cerion, tenor; Ray, tenor; Bert, bari; Lester, trombone; Robert, bari-horn; David, bass; Sherman, bass; Wilbur, bass; Everett, drums; Greg, drums; CoJoe, congas; Horace, piano and cond.; Nate, piano; Spirits, percussion and time; Glenda, voice; Patricia, voice; Linda, voice. Compositions: E.P. -- Azar.
    - Concert at Joseph Pomeroy Widney High School, 1970 November 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Society for the Preservation of Black Music. Compositions: Havey Karma -- Going to Meet H.B. -- For Fats -- Bunke.
      Sherman McKinney Quartet. Personnel includes: Michael Stanton, piano; Paul Wright, bass; Raymond Pounds, drums; Sherman McKinney, soprano sax, electric piano, bass.
    - The UGMAA Show, 11/14/1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      Personnel: Sherman, Effie, Cheryl and Omatie
      Free Form Quintent
      Personnel: Lino, piano, cornet and french horn; Will, alto sax, flute; Yusef, bass; Tylan, percussion
      Compositions: Effi, Horace Speaks, Freedom, Effendi (McCoy Tyner, arr by HT), In A Sentimental Mood
    - Widney H.S., 11/29/1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Guido Sinclair Quartet
      Compositions: Black, Brown and Yellow (Guido Sinclair)
    - Mr. San Antonio College, 12/03/1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; David B.; Ike Williams, trumpet, flugelhorn; Everett; Edwin Pleasant, alto sax, flute
      Compositions: Resurrection, Pearl, World Peace, Effi
    - Widney H.S. (24th and Gramercy), 12/13/1970; 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      The Suns of Lite (band - Nate's band)
      Personnel: Nate, piano; Curtis Daniels, vibes; Nate Davis, alto sax, bass, flute; Semade, drums; Fritz Wise, drums; Roho, congas
      Compositions: Shekina (Nate), Presence of God, Black Woman (Nate), St. James (Curtis Daniels), Shots in Dark (Nate Davis), Her (Nate)
    - Widney H.S. (24th and Gramercy), 12/13/1970; 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      Compositions: Her, Sometimes (or Something, by Nate Davis)
      Other band